<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
  <pages>
    <title>about</title>
    <date>2023-01-14</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/about/</permalink>
    
    <body>&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-this&quot;&gt;what is this?&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A website hosted on Github Pages (&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;emily-flambe&#x2F;emily-flambe.github.io&quot;&gt;emily-flambe.github.io&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;), generated with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;getzola&#x2F;zola&quot;&gt;Zola&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; using the theme &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;kyoheiu&#x2F;emily_zola_theme&quot;&gt;emily-zola-theme&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-are-you&quot;&gt;who are you??&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flambe (she&#x2F;her).&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently I am an Engineering Manager for &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.communitytechalliance.org&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Community Tech Alliance&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. The rest of my professional history is &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.linkedin.com&#x2F;in&#x2F;emilycogsdill&#x2F;&quot;&gt;on LinkedIn&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But also: what is the measure of a person?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-do-i-reach-you&quot;&gt;how do I reach you???&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;m sure you&#x27;ll find a way&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Hot Skiing Tips</title>
    <date>2023-01-14</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20230114-hot-skiing-tips/</permalink>
    <description>Make your skiing a more ~glamourous~ experience</description>
    <body>&lt;h1 id=&quot;lip-plumper&quot;&gt;Lip Plumper&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lip balm is for normos. Use lip plumper instead.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It keeps your lips hydrated, and the &amp;quot;plumping&amp;quot; effect (can we please find another word though?) is achieved using an irritant, such as capsaicin, that will make your lips tingly and warm!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why aren&#x27;t more people talking about this??&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;wigs&quot;&gt;Wigs&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can wear a wig under your helmet! There&#x27;s no rule against it!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wigs are warm and they make you look like you put a lot of effort into your hair, which people think is a good thing for some reason.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joke&#x27;s on them, you&#x27;re just wearing a sexy hair hat!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;get-really-good-at-skiing&quot;&gt;Get really good at skiing&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively: drink hot cider and wait for your friends. That sounds nice.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>St. Moritz</title>
    <date>2023-01-08</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20230108-st-moritz/</permalink>
    <description>Notes from my solo trip to go skiing in St. Moritz, Switzerland.</description>
    <body>&lt;h1 id=&quot;st-moritz&quot;&gt;St. Moritz&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I traveled to St. Moritz for a (very brief) ski trip in early January 2023. Much has been written about the destination, and much can be easily discovered through the usual tools for finding information on the World Wide Web. But if you want to see my (sparse and not particularly useful) notes, &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;docs.google.com&#x2F;document&#x2F;d&#x2F;1gA-YeZjsPQ2yW5RyN_cXtltzSBUjlaW-WMst0X_KgR4&#x2F;edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here they are&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a publicly accessible Google Document. You can share it with anyone you wish, although it&#x27;s not clear why you would.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Zermatt</title>
    <date>2023-01-07</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20230107-zermatt/</permalink>
    <description>Notes from my solo trip to go skiing in Zermatt, Switzerland.</description>
    <body>&lt;h1 id=&quot;zermatt&quot;&gt;Zermatt&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I traveled to Zermatt for a quick ski trip in early January 2023. The town is everything I ever wanted in a Swiss ski destination, yet I found it moderately quirky to navigate (though ultimately not actually difficult).&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I documented my experiences and some pro tips in the form of &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;docs.google.com&#x2F;document&#x2F;d&#x2F;1_v2DzwsOsAcBgXiTKrh_rrsbSYpgoEQUEbbrNScCG6E&#x2F;edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;this Google Document&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. The URL is publicly available and you are welcome to share it with anyone you wish, should you (like me) find the existing travel blogs and Reddit threads annoying to navigate.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Carol the Crow</title>
    <date>2022-12-26</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20221226-carol-the-crow/</permalink>
    <description>Something absurd I wrote that might not even be factually correct idk</description>
    <body>&lt;p&gt;The 2020 South Carolina Democratic presidential primary is widely considered to have been a turning point in what was, as you certainly recall, a chaotic and uncertain primary season. Democrats were in disarray, though by the end of February, most podcasters and watercooler conversationalists were in agreement that the nominee would likely be Sanders or Warren, leaving what remained of the crowded field limping along on the fumes of rapidly fading hope.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On February 29, 2020, the morning of the South Carolina primary, a staffer for the Biden campaign headed into the office of campaign HQ in Philadelphia. To her dismay, as she reached to open the door to the front entrance, she noticed the lifeless corpse of a crow that had evidently flown into the glass. What had mere moments ago been a vibrant creature of the Earth was now an inert heap of disheveled feathers twitching in the icy wind.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This staffer was the director of reporting and analytics. Her task was to wield Data and Numbers to derive insights normally inaccessible to our limited human awareness. Yet her professional commitment to empiricism could not stave off the creeping tendrils of a superstitious foreboding. For what portend could possibly be more inauspicious than a dead bird, killed in an instant by its inability to see what was plainly obvious to everyone else: that its path forward was no path at all, but a solid and unforgiving barrier?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outcome of that day was, of course, the exact opposite of what the bird portended. And this complete inversion of expectations, superstitious though they were, was (perhaps unsurprisingly) transmuted into a different superstition entirely. The crow’s death seemed a taunting echo of the dominant narratives about Biden - that he was just an old man tilting at windmills, a blind bird taking a flight of delusion that would certainly be his last. But the crow - or rather, the tale it seemed to tell - was wrong. And, for the first time, it seemed the podcasters and watercooler conversationalists might be wrong as well.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crow was posthumously named Carol for its appearance on the morning of the South Carolina primary. A state named after a Caroline (actually King Charles I, but that&#x27;s beside the point), and a Carol named after that state, all possessed a delicious circularity that mirrored the twisted divinity of the day’s events.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus began a venerated campaign tradition of throwing Carol at a window on the morning of each state&#x27;s primary election. (Carol the Crow was represented in effigy by a crow plushie, though taxidermy was considered.) Super Tuesday followed shortly after the South Carolina primary and cemented Biden&#x27;s place at the front of the pack, which persisted until his ultimate victory.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tradition continued in the General Election as well, in which, like the primaries, different states began opening up early voting at different times. And on each occasion, all staff would receive a calendar invite for a 5-minute meeting, in which the staffer who first came across that hapless crow would gently toss Carol-in-effigy against a window. It was our way of remembering how far the team had come, particularly those who had worked on the primary and whose nerves had been hopelessly frayed long before the General Election even began. And it was our way of sharing a moment of reverence and hope while disguising the emotional weight of each anxious occasion in a ritual that was objectively absurd.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campaigns attract people who are able to hold in their hearts both a commitment to rational inquiry and a dash (or a dollop) of magical thinking, the two dueling like serpents on the caduceus. After all, a campaign cannot hope to win without making intelligent use of the data it has available, but no campaign can ever hope to have enough data to predict the unpredictable, the October Surprises, the polling errors and modeling deficiencies that you know are mis-calibrating your expectations but which you are powerless to intercept.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campaigns also attract people who cope with stress through humor, and there is very obvious humor in the act of ritually throwing a stuffed animal at a window.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most staffers on the Biden campaign had mixed feelings about Biden as a candidate - we were pragmatists, by and large, who figured he was our best shot at defeating Trump. We were united in purpose, but not in a deeply held passion for our candidate. Carol the Crow thus attained a meaning and symbolism that transcended the man (and woman) we were trying to elect. The throwing of the Crow was more than a plushie doinking against a window in some faraway office - each doink was a fresh defiance of defeatism and despair.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it told a tale of death, transfiguration, and resurrection - because while that crow&#x27;s life ended on the steps of Biden HQ on February 29, 2020, Carol the Crow took on a life of her own, which continues in the hearts of all who bore witness.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;don&#x27;t forget to like and subscribe&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Biking around Taiwan</title>
    <date>2022-11-26</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20221126-taiwan-bike-trip/</permalink>
    <description>Documentation from a gloriously impulsive trip I took to ride bikes across rural Taiwan. (Private Google Doc)</description>
    <body>&lt;p&gt;November 2022 was... well, it sure was a month.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The highlight of the season was a gloriously impulsive trip to Taiwan, an adventure documented in &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;docs.google.com&#x2F;document&#x2F;d&#x2F;1OPMFOCFDlDr7_vRhkSO-e8Y21N764frs--YvALPCx1w&#x2F;edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;this Google Doc&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>MathJax Support</title>
    <date>2021-01-03</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/draft/mathjax-support/</permalink>
    
    <body>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please add the following lines in the front matter when using MathJax.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;z-code&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-text z-plain&quot;&gt;[extra]
math = true
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;hr &#x2F;&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;euler-s-identity&quot;&gt;Euler&#x27;s identity&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$e^{i\pi }+1=0$&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;geometric-interpretation&quot;&gt;Geometric interpretation&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any complex number $z=x+iy$ can be represented by the point $(x,y)$ on the complex plane. This point can also be represented in polar coordinates as $(r,\theta )$, where $r$ is the absolute value of $z$ (distance from the origin), and $\theta$  is the argument of $z$ (angle counterclockwise from the positive x-axis). By the definitions of sine and cosine, this point has cartesian coordinates of $(r\cos \theta ,r\sin \theta )$, implying that $z=r(\cos \theta +i\sin \theta )$. According to Euler&#x27;s formula, this is equivalent to saying $z=re^{i\theta}$.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Euler&#x27;s identity says that $-1=e^{i\pi }$. Since $e^{i\pi }$ is $re^{i\theta }$ for $r$ = 1 and $\theta =\pi$ , this can be interpreted as a fact about the number −1 on the complex plane: its distance from the origin is 1, and its angle from the positive x-axis is $\pi$ radians.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;en.wikipedia.org&#x2F;wiki&#x2F;Euler%27s_identity&quot;&gt;Euler&#x27;s identity - Wikipedia&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
    <date>2021-01-02</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/draft/markdown-syntax-guide/</permalink>
    
    <body>&lt;h3 id=&quot;headings&quot;&gt;Headings&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following HTML &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; is the highest section level while &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt; is the lowest.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;h1&quot;&gt;H1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;h2&quot;&gt;H2&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;h3&quot;&gt;H3&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;h4&quot;&gt;H4&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;h5&quot;&gt;H5&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;h6&quot;&gt;H6&lt;&#x2F;h6&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt;Paragraph&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga. Ri oditatquam, ad quibus unda veliamenimin cusam et facea ipsamus es exerum sitate dolores editium rerore eost, temped molorro ratiae volorro te reribus dolorer sperchicium faceata tiustia prat.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itatur? Quiatae cullecum rem ent aut odis in re eossequodi nonsequ idebis ne sapicia is sinveli squiatum, core et que aut hariosam ex eat.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;inline code block&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;pre data-lang=&quot;rust&quot; class=&quot;language-rust z-code&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-rust&quot; data-lang=&quot;rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-source z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-keyword z-other z-rust&quot;&gt;use&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-path z-rust&quot;&gt;std&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-accessor z-rust&quot;&gt;::&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;io&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-storage z-type z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;fn&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; &lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-entity z-name z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;main&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-parameters z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-parameters z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-parameters z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-parameters z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt; &lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-block z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-block z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;{&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-macro z-rust&quot;&gt;println!&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-string z-quoted z-double z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;Guess the number!&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;

    &lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-macro z-rust&quot;&gt;println!&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-string z-quoted z-double z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;Please input your guess.&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;

    &lt;span class=&quot;z-storage z-type z-rust&quot;&gt;let&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;z-storage z-modifier z-rust&quot;&gt;mut&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; guess &lt;span class=&quot;z-keyword z-operator z-assignment z-rust&quot;&gt;=&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-type z-rust&quot;&gt;String&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-path z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-accessor z-rust&quot;&gt;::&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;new&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;

    &lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-path z-rust&quot;&gt;io&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-accessor z-rust&quot;&gt;::&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;stdin&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-accessor z-dot z-rust&quot;&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;read_line&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-keyword z-operator z-bitwise z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-storage z-modifier z-rust&quot;&gt;mut&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; guess&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-accessor z-dot z-rust&quot;&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-function z-rust&quot;&gt;expect&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-string z-quoted z-double z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;Failed to read line&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;

    &lt;span class=&quot;z-support z-macro z-rust&quot;&gt;println!&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;(&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-string z-quoted z-double z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-begin z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;You guessed: &lt;span class=&quot;z-constant z-other z-placeholder z-rust&quot;&gt;{}&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-definition z-string z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-group z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-separator z-rust&quot;&gt;,&lt;&#x2F;span&gt; guess&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-group z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-terminator z-rust&quot;&gt;;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-meta z-block z-rust&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;z-punctuation z-section z-block z-end z-rust&quot;&gt;}&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;span&gt;&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;&lt;&#x2F;pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;First Header&lt;&#x2F;th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Second Header&lt;&#x2F;th&gt;&lt;&#x2F;tr&gt;&lt;&#x2F;thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Content from cell 1&lt;&#x2F;td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Content from cell 2&lt;&#x2F;td&gt;&lt;&#x2F;tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Content in the first column&lt;&#x2F;td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Content in the second column&lt;&#x2F;td&gt;&lt;&#x2F;tr&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;tbody&gt;&lt;&#x2F;table&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;ordered-list&quot;&gt;Ordered List&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First item&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second item&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Third item&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;unordered-list&quot;&gt;Unordered List&lt;&#x2F;h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List item&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another item&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And another item
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;orange&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;apple
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;banana&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;watermelon&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Welcome to emily, a KISS theme for Zola</title>
    <date>2020-12-31</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/draft/welcome-to-emily/</permalink>
    
    <body>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
  <pages>
    <title>Pacific Crest Trail</title>
    <date>2019-09-01</date>
    <permalink>https://emily-flambe.github.io/post/20190901-pct/</permalink>
    <description>Blog posts from my hike in 2019. Mostly incoherent and unhinged. Nice photos though</description>
    <body>&lt;p&gt;In 2019 I hiked 2000 miles of the Pacific Crest Trail. Along the way, I maintained a blog with daily posts that were generally poorly-written and a tad unhinged.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I paid someone a few bucks to migrate the whole thing to &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;docs.google.com&#x2F;document&#x2F;d&#x2F;1_QRHPQf7KDRlDLnUlxozcww0CU8tKC1HWdsqTrIZilo&#x2F;edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;this Google Doc&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</body>
  </pages>
  
</root>
